GET IT ON

* |
* |

* SHOP ONLINE

    Women's Most Popular

    Men's Most Popular

    Designer Favorites

    Collections

    Shop by Category

    Discover More

* 

Menu

Use your location to find centers near you

* Shop Online
    
    Women's Most Popular

    Men's Most Popular

    Designer Favorites

    Collections

    Shop by Category

    Discover More

      Find Nearby Centers

Quick Links

Find Nearby Centers [See All Properties](https://www.simon.com/mall "See All Properties") [Mall Insider](https://www.simon.com/mall-insider "Mall Insider") [VIP Club](https://www.premiumoutlets.com/vip "VIP Club")

Suggested Results

Legal Information & Notices

PRIVACY  
POLICY
================

### LEGAL NOTICES

Terms of Use Privacy Policy California Privacy Rights Canada Privacy Rights Colorado Privacy Rights Cookie Policy Web Accessibility Statement API Terms of Use Code of Conduct Code of Business Conduct & Ethics Digital Assets Terms of Use Directories & Screens Privacy Policy Diversity & Inclusion Policy Mobile Text Terms of Use Opt Out/Unsubscribe Assistance Retailer Showcase Terms of Use Social Media Guidelines Suppliers Code of Conduct Tax Documents Access Agreement User Generated Content Terms of Use VIP Passport Participation Agreement Wi-Fi Terms of Use

Last Updated: September 20, 2024

Table of Contents
=================

What this Privacy Policy Covers
===============================

This Privacy Policy (also referred to as “**Notice**”) describes what personal information we collect, how we collect and use your personal information, to whom we disclose your personal information and why, the measures we take to protect your personal information, and the choices you may have regarding our use of your personal information. This Notice covers our websites, mobile apps, and related services where this Notice is posted (“**Sites**”), which are located in and made available exclusively for users located in the United States and Puerto Rico. You agree that your use of our Sites signifies that you have read and consent to our Terms of Use and to the collection, use, and sharing of your information as detailed in this Notice, which is an integral part of our Terms of Use.

Personal Information We Collect
===============================

We collect or receive the types of personal information in the following list, which depends on the products or services you use from us, as well as your device or account settings. Not all types of personal information listed below will be collected or received about every person who visits our Sites and we will not collect any information that is prohibited by, or for which we cannot gather adequate consent under, applicable law.

* **Basic Personal Contact Information**, such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, and other similar basic identifiers;
* **Device and Account Identifiers,** such as account login information, Media Access Control (“**MAC**”) address(es), Internet Protocol (“**IP**”) address, cookie IDs, mobile ad IDs, device or software settings and version information, and social media account information;
* **Internet Usage Information**, such as your browsing or search activity as well as your interactions with our websites, mobile applications, emails, or advertisements, your methods of accessing this information (to determine if you are a human or a bot) such as your ability to recognize visual patterns or your keyboard, mouse, touchpad, and/or touchscreen usage patterns;
* **Commercial Transaction Information**, such as purchase and transaction history information (such as products or services you have purchased or returned, the price and taxes paid, and shipping information), product reviews, and sweepstakes and contest entries;
* **Communication Detail**, such as content of communications to or from Simon, public communications you make, or communications where Simon is otherwise included or copied such as emails, text messages, call or chat logs, social media posts or direct messages, online reviews, survey responses, voicemail and recorded phone calls, mailed letters, calendar information, or other similar communications;
* **Demographic Information**, such as age, gender, citizenship, ethnicity, date of birth, family or marital status, household income, education, professional and employment information, shopping or other preferences, and other demographic information;
* **Financial Information,** such as credit or debit card numbers, bank account numbers, and payment preferences;
* **Biometric Information**, such as your facial geometry (NOTE: we do not collect this information in the State of Illinois);
* **Geolocation:** the imprecise location of your device (which may be inferred from your IP address, for example) and, if you have provided consent, the precise location of your device (inferred from your received signal strength to Wi-Fi access points or Bluetooth beacons, for example). For more information about precise geolocation, see the [_How We Collect Personal Information_ _>_ _We Collect it Automatically_](#we-collect-it-automatically) section below;
* **Audio-visual Information:** Audio, visual, and other sensory information such as photographs, audio, video, and thermal scans that records or depicts your likeness, voice, or other sensory information about you or your vehicle (such as license plate information); and
* **Identification and Background Check Information:** Government-issued identifiers and identification (e.g., national identification numbers, driver’s license numbers), background and criminal check information, such as reported credit history and criminal convictions; and
* **Inferences**, analyses, targeted-marketing audience segments, reports, and other models based on any of the information listed above such shopping or Site usage patterns and behaviors.

How We Use Your Personal Information
====================================

We use personal information we collect for purposes related to operating and improving our Sites and providing products and services to you and third parties such as:

* Providing services such as customer and technical support, account set-up and maintenance, processing and communicating with you regarding payments, orders, transactions, and the products and services we provide;
* Verifying your identity;
* Advertising (including targeted advertising based on your preferences) of products and services of us or third parties to you;
* Monitoring, analysis, and auditing of transactions, user engagement and behavior, Site functionality, and advertising to audit and ensure compliance and effectiveness;
* Responding to communications or interactions with you and providing you transient services such as non-targeted advertising while you interact with our Sites;
* Maintaining the safety, security, quality, and integrity of our Sites, products, and services and detecting or preventing fraud and illegal activities;
* Verifying and maintaining the quality or safety of our services or devices and improving, upgrade, or enhance them;
* Debugging and other activities to maintain, correct, or improve the quality of our systems and online services;
* Conducting business analysis, such as analytics, projections, identifying areas for operational and programmatic improvement;
* Logging and analyzing interactions with our Sites to understand how you interact with our Sites to personalize the user experience and content (including advertising and messaging campaigns);
* Utilizing analysis, machine learning, algorithms, business intelligence and analytics software, and artificial intelligence to make or compile inferences, analyses, targeted-marketing audience segments, and reports based on identifiable and aggregated non-identifiable personal information to improve our products and services and for advertising;
* Processing employment application, including verifying statements made on any application and performing background and credit checks;
* Conducting research and development, including undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration; and
* Maintaining compliance with legal and regulatory requirements, investigating, defending, or prosecuting claims or disputes relating to our Sites or other properties, products, or services.

How We Collect Personal Information
===================================

We collect and compile personal information from multiple sources, both online and offline, directly and from third-party sources using different devices, sources, and technologies.

You Provide it to Us
--------------------

When you interact with or visit one of our Sites you may provide us personal information while engaging in activities such as:

* Creating an account on, interact with, and/or provide search terms or preferences on one of our websites, mobile services, or interactive screens or directories at our retail shopping destinations (e.g., the Simon mobile app, Simon Search®, the Simon Mall Insider®, the Premium Outlets VIP Shopper Club®, or the Simon Mobile Shopper Club)
* Purchasing Simon® Giftcards;
* Signing-up and/or participating in our programs or promotions, such as the Simon® American Express® Credit Card program;
* Contacting us for customer support or any other purpose, including by the use of voicemail or call recording technology (in compliance with applicable law);
* Posting content to one of our websites, mobile services, or social media pages such as solicited or unsolicited content you generate, ratings, reviews, feedback, or contest or survey entries;
* Participating in a contest, sweepstake, promotion, or survey;
* Signing-up to connect to the “# Free Simon Wi-Fi" network, which we provide for your use; and
* Interacting with or using services on our websites, mobile applications, or interactive screens or directories in our retail shopping destinations that rely on audio, video, or photographic images you supply though our device’s or your device’s camera(s) or microphone(s) or recordings you otherwise make and submit to us to provide you a service (e.g., promotional social media filters, virtual photo frames, product scanning, or voice search).

We Collect it Automatically
---------------------------

When you visit our Sites or interact with our advertising or other communications with you (such as clicking a link in an advertisement or e-mail), we automatically gather personal information about you such as device and account identifiers and internet or network usage information. 

Unless prohibited by applicable law, we gather precise geolocation information from your device using technologies deployed in our retail shopping destinations such as Wi-Fi and Bluetooth beacons if your device’s location sharing settings (which you can change) allow it. Bluetooth beacons allow us to show you products that may interest you based on your preferences or other data we have collected about you.

If your device has GPS enabled and you have allowed your GPS location to be shared with us or you otherwise indicate your position or preferred retail shopping destination on an interactive map or drop-down on one of our Sites including services such as Simon Search, we can show you the Simon retail shopping destination(s) closest to you and can provide you a path to navigating through such retail shopping destination(s) to store(s) that contains item(s) of interest to you (based on search terms and results or preferences you provide to us). 

We Get it from Businesses Affiliated with Us
--------------------------------------------

Companies that share common ownership or management control or that are our partners in certain ventures (“**Affiliates**”) may share information with us about you.

We Get it from Unaffiliated Third-party Sources and Public Material
-------------------------------------------------------------------

We get additional personal information about you from third-party or publicly available sources (such as third-party device and browsing data, bot detection results, social media posts, and background and public record search results), with the aim of enhancing the accuracy and completeness of our records, verifying your identity, qualifying you for services, refining the quality and customization of our services, enhancing the attractiveness and relevance of our advertisements, to fight spam and abuse, and bolstering our fraud prevention efforts.

Who We Disclose Personal Information to and Why
===============================================

We disclose the types of personal information described in the [_Personal Information We Collect_](#personal-information-we-collect) section above with the types of third parties described below.

Businesses Affiliated with Us
-----------------------------

We disclose your personal information with Affiliates for the promotion or cross promotion of our Sites or other products and services of us or our Affiliates, or to provide to Affiliates or receive from an Affiliates the types of services described in the rest of this section.

Service, Technology, and Advertising Vendors
--------------------------------------------

For the purposes described below, we disclose personal information to the types of vendors described below, which may be Affiliates in some cases. We also provide insights and other related aggregated non-identifiable data and reports (“**Insights**”) to the vendors listed below and potential or existing retail tenants at our Sites. These Insights are produced by compiling and analyzing (by manual or computational means and by us or a vendor) the personal information of many individuals (e.g., the shopping preferences, demographics, or transactions of many users) from any combination of the sources referenced in the [_How We Collect Personal Information_](#how-we-collect-personal-information) section above from which we will remove information identifying you before sharing. We may receive payment for these Insights. In the event we disclose your personal information with any third-party business or vendor for any other purpose not referenced in this Notice, we will obtain your affirmative consent or provide you prior notice in compliance with applicable law.

Providers of Service to Us
--------------------------

We provide personal information to vendors that provide services to us such as third-party payment processors, point-of-sale software and hardware providers, order fulfillment and shipping vendors, security and management companies, providers of localized content and video or other content recommendations, employment applications, recruitment vendors, verification vendors, and technical or administrative vendors that help us host, maintain, secure, analyze, improve, and fight spam and abuse of our Sites.

Providers of Service to You
---------------------------

We provide personal information to vendors that provide services directly to you that we may refer or market to you. Some of these services may be co-branded with our trade names or logos such as the Simon® American Express® Credit Card program, Shop.Simon.com, and our Simon Giftcard® order site (for individual consumers). We may receive compensation for such co-branded services. These direct service vendors, whether co-branded or not, maintain their own separate privacy notices (posted on their website or mobile app) and are prohibited from using the personal information we disclose to them for any purpose other than providing products and services that are agreed upon with us.

Advertising and Data Technology Vendors
---------------------------------------

We provide personal information to advertising vendors such as advertisers, marketing service providers and agencies, advertising technology and retail media network (“**Ad Tech**”) providers, and website, mobile application, and social media usage analytics platforms with which we, advertisers, or our collaborators work. 

* **Advertisers**. We provide opportunities at our Sites for businesses to advertise to you in various physical or digital formats. Digital advertisements we provide to advertisers may include pixels, cookies, or other tracking technologies that collect information about you to analyze the effectiveness of such ads. 
* **Digital Media Providers**. We disclose personal information with providers of external websites (e.g., entertainment, news, Affiliates, and search websites), mobile applications, and social media platforms that you may visit to help us serve relevant ads to you on such digital media outlets and to help us analyze the effectiveness of such ads. 
* **Ad Tech Providers**. We provide personal information to Ad Tech providers including without limitation, data activation, curation, and identity platform providers, and digital (e.g., email, website, mobile device and application) advertising agencies, buyers, sellers, and technology and research providers such as Adento. These Ad Tech providers may employ cookies, pixels, beacons, device geolocation and MAC and IP address identifiers over Wi-Fi, and similar technologies to serve you targeted advertising either on or external to our Sites. For more information about how to set your interest-based advertising preferences, see [_How to Set Your Preferences_ > _Interest-based Advertising_](#how-to-set-your-preferences)
* **Data Technology Providers**. We provide personal information to providers of data management, automation, and analysis technology such as customer relationship management platform providers, and providers of automation, analysis, machine learning, algorithm, and business and artificial intelligence data services.
* **Analytics Providers**. We provide personal information that is aggregated by providers of analytics regarding traffic at and performance of our Sites and retail shopping destinations and the effectiveness of our advertising such as [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites) and [AisleLabs](https://www.aislelabs.com/privacy/).

Government, regulatory, or law enforcement agencies
---------------------------------------------------

We will disclose your personal information to government, regulatory, or law enforcement agencies if we believe the disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with regulatory or legal requirements, or to protect against, or aid in the investigation, prosecution, or defense of, any alleged crime, any alleged threat or violation of our or any third party’s safety, or property, legal, equitable, human, or other rights in any way related to our Sites.

Business Successors
-------------------

If we sell all or a part of our company, are part of a merger, consolidation, restructuring, sale of company stock, sale of assets, bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding, or other corporate change, your personal information may be transferred as part of that transaction. In the event of any such corporate change, we will use reasonable efforts to make sure your information is handled by any successor in accordance with this Notice.

Other Parties and the Public
----------------------------

If you choose to disclose personal information when you contribute content publicly through message boards, blogs, social media, reviews, or similar public forums on or related to the Sites or you create an account for a service on the Sites and indicate that you consent to sharing with other users of such service profile information such as your username, birthday, interests, or other content you enter in such service, we may continue to disclose any such content and voluntarily-provided personal information within such forums without any obligation or liability to you unless you have properly requested any relevant personal information deletion rights pursuant to applicable law.

How to Set Your Preferences
===========================

Please note that the methods of opt-out referenced in this section may only work per browser and/or per device requiring you to request such opt outs from multiple browsers and/or devices.

Marketing Communications
------------------------

We may periodically send you promotional materials or notifications related to our Sites or our, our Affiliates’, or third-party advertisers’ other products and services if you opt-in (provide advance consent) to receiving such marketing communications from us. We send such promotional materials or notifications by mail or electronic means such as e-mail, website, social media, and mobile (push, text, or in-app) notifications including contextual and interest-based (targeted) advertising.

### To Opt-out or Unsubscribe

If you no longer wish to receive promotional marketing materials from us, you may opt out of receiving such materials by the following methods:

* **In General**: To opt-out from our marketing communications, in general, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our opt-out form. If, and to the extent we are able and allowed to detect that, you are accessing any of the Sites from an applicable jurisdiction that requires it, we will display a banner on this site with a cookie preference, privacy notice, and opt-out menu.
* **Email (only)**: To unsubscribe from marketing emails from us (only) click on the unsubscribe link in the footer of the email you received or the website on which you created the related account.
* **Text Messages (only)**: You may unsubscribe from text (SMS and MMS) messages by following the prompt provided on our messages or by sending a text to **74666** (SIMON) with the word **STOP**. We will work to comply with your request promptly.

Interest-Based Advertising
--------------------------

Interest-based (or targeted) ads are ads optimized for you based on your preferences or inferences we or advertising vendors make about you. For more information about interest-based advertising, see the [_Advertising and Data Technology Vendors_](#advertising-and-data-technology-vendors) section above. To adjust your interest-based advertising preferences, follow the instructions below:

* **Opt out of Simon interest-based ads by changing your preferences.** [Click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our general opt-out form or, if you are a resident of a State referenced in our [_State Privacy Rights_](#state-privacy-rights) section below, click on _Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information and Opt Out of Targeted Advertising_ here or in the footer of this page. Our Sites may respond to the Global Privacy Control (“**GPC**”) signal from your browser but not other types of “**do not track**” signals. You may have to accept our cookies when asked for your cookie preferences for these opt-outs to work.
* **Opt out of interest-based ads on your mobile device**. Mobile devices offer options for opting in or out of interest-based advertising. Please refer to your device settings and instructions for additional information.
* **Opt out of interest-based ads from third-party advertisers that participate in industry groups.** See the websites of the [National Advertising Initiative](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/)or the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) to opt out of interest-based ads from their participant companies, which does not guarantee that you will not see interested-based ads from other companies either on the Sites or elsewhere.

Even if you opt out by one of the methods in this section of the Notice, you may still receive communications from us (i) by other methods and on browsers or devices for which you have not opted out or (ii) regarding an order you place, customer support request you make, or other communication directed to or relevant to us that you initiate before or after you make an opt out request.

How to Access and Update Your Personal Information
==================================================

If you are a resident of an applicable jurisdiction, see our [_State Privacy Rights_](#state-privacy-rights) or [_Canadian Privacy Rights_](#canadian-privacy-rights) section below to learn how to access your rights regarding personal information that we have collected or you have provided to us.

How We Secure Your Personal Information
=======================================

We use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures designed to safeguard information in our possession against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. We take reasonable measures to limit access to this data to authorized personnel who need to know that information in order to perform, develop, or improve our services and Platform.

However, the confidentiality of information transmitted over the Internet cannot be guaranteed. We urge you to exercise caution when transmitting Personal Information over the Internet. **WE CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT UNAUTHORIZED THIRD PARTIES WILL NOT GAIN ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION; THEREFORE, WHEN SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.**

International Transfers of Personal Information
===============================================

We are based in the United States. Any information you provide to us through use of the Sites may be stored and processed, transferred between, and accessed outside the jurisdiction where you reside, including in the United States and other countries which may not guarantee the same level of protection of personal information as the one in which you reside. We may need to send your personal information overseas as part of our normal business operations. Provided the data protection laws of these other countries differ from those in the United States, please be assured that we take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.

How Long We Retain Your Personal Information
============================================

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to provide our services, including the Sites, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. We will not retain your personal information longer than reasonably necessary for the purposes for which the information was collected.

Children’s Privacy
==================

Our Sites are for a general audience, not targeted to children, and we do not solicit or knowingly collect personal information from children 13 years of age or younger.

Please contact us if you have concerns regarding the potential collection of your child’s information.

Links to External Sites and Content
===================================

We may provide links to external content sources that are not owned or operated by us such as websites, mobile applications, and streaming or other media content platforms maintained by Affiliates, external businesses, governmental units, or individuals. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of these external content sources. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy notices and practices of the providers of such external content sources, which are not governed by this Notice.

State Privacy Rights
====================

California Privacy Rights
-------------------------

Visit our [_California Privacy Notices_](https://www.simon.com/legal/privacy/california) for provisions, which supplement this Notice, regarding your privacy rights if you are a resident of California.

Colorado Privacy Rights
-----------------------

Visit our [_Colorado Privacy Notices_](https://www.simon.com/legal/privacy/colorado) for provisions, which supplement this Notice, regarding your privacy rights if you are a resident of Colorado.

Connecticut Privacy Rights
--------------------------

Connecticut residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Connecticut resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision. If your appeal is denied or if you have any concerns about the results of your appeal you may contact the Connecticut Attorney General [here](https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page).

Delaware Privacy Rights
-----------------------

Delaware residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Delaware resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Iowa Privacy Rights
-------------------

Iowa residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Iowa resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Montana Privacy Rights
----------------------

Montana residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Montana resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Nebraska Privacy Rights
-----------------------

Nebraska residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Nebraska resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Nevada Privacy Rights
---------------------

If you are a Nevada resident, You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app.

New Hampshire Privacy Rights
----------------------------

New Hampshire residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a New Hampshire resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

New Jersey Privacy Rights
-------------------------

New Jersey residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a New Jersey resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 45 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Oregon Privacy Rights
---------------------

Oregon residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Oregon resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 45 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Texas Privacy Rights
--------------------

Texas residents can exercise the following rights:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Texas resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision.

Utah Privacy Rights
-------------------

Utah residents can exercise the following rights by going to the footer of our website and selecting the “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information and Opt Out of Targeted Advertising link or going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Utah resident, [**click here**](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision. If your appeal is denied or if you have any concerns about the results of your appeal you may contact the Utah Attorney General [here](https://attorneygeneral.utah.gov/data-privacy/).

Virginia Privacy Rights
-----------------------

Virginia residents can exercise the following rights by going to the footer of our website and selecting the “_Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information and Opt Out of Targeted Advertising_” link or going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app:

* Request to Confirm Whether My Personal Information Is Processed
* Request to Access My Personal Information
* Delete My Personal Information
* Correct My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising
* Opt Out of the Sale of My Personal Information
* Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Certain Profiling

You can also request any of these rights by submitting a request through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at +1 (888) 914-9661 (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted). You can also adjust your settings or opt-out by by going to Settings > Adjust Data & Privacy Settings in the Simon mobile app. Once we receive your request, we must verify your identity and will respond within 45 days after receipt of your request (extended by an additional 45 days where necessary). If we decline to act on one of your rights as a Virginia resident, [click here](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) to fill out our online form and request an appeal. Within 60 days after receipt of your appeal, we shall inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including an explanation of the reasons for our decision. If your appeal is denied or if you have any concerns about the results of your appeal you may contact the Virginia Attorney General [here](https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint).

Canadian Privacy Rights
=======================

Visit our [_Canada Privacy Notices_](https://www.simon.com/legal/privacy/canada) for provisions regarding your privacy rights if you are a resident of a province of Canada.

Updates to this Privacy Policy
==============================

We update this Notice from time to time. Below is a description of the most recent changes to this , which were made effective as of the Last Update date referenced at the top of this Notice.

Recent Updates to this Notice
-----------------------------

* Added new provisions to the State Privacy Rights section for Delaware, Iowa, Maryland, Minnesota, Montana, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Nebraska, Nevada, Oregon, Tennessee, Texas.
* Updated Contact Us information

Contact Us
==========

We welcome all requests, suggestions, and questions concerning our use of your personal Information. For all inquiries in regards to privacy of your personal information, contact us through our online [Privacy & Data Request Form](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/80ecbc6e-7e6b-4595-8581-8c2c595a58d9/334a81ba-4130-4922-90c2-15520194ef75) or by phone at [+1 (888) 914-9661](tel:+18889149661) (enter the required PIN number of 187828 when prompted), or send us a letter to:

Simon Media Properties, LLC  
Attention: Data Privacy Officer  
225 W Washington St  
Indianapolis, IN 46204-3435 USA

Back To Top

This is a dialog window which overlays the main content of the page. The modal begins with a heading 2 called "DEALS, EVENTS AND MORE". Pressing the Close Modal button at the bottom of the modal will close the modal and bring you back to where you were on the page.

DEALS, EVENTS  
AND MORE.  
PLUS, IT’S FREE.
--------------------------------------------

Get the inside scoop (and a chance at a **$1,000 shopping spree**) today.

EMAIL ADDRESS: Required  

BECOME A MALL INSIDER

#### DEALS. EVENTS.  
EXCLUSIVE OFFERS!

Become a Simon Mall Insider® today for the  
chance to win a $1,000 shopping spree!

EMAIL ADDRESS: Required  JOIN

* * *

ShopSimon™

Simon Giftcards®

For Businesses

For Investors

For Job Seekers

More From Simon

COPYRIGHT© 1999-2024, SIMON MEDIA PROPERTIES, LLC ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.  
By continuing past this page and/or using this site, you agree to abide by the [Terms of Use](https://www.simon.com/legal "View Simon's Terms of Use") for this site, which prohibit commercial use of any information on this site.

* Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information and Opt Out of Targeted Advertising
